[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these hairstyles the sides and back of the hair are kept short, while the front is kept long and combed forward?", "correct_answer": "Devilock", "incorrect_answers": ["Hi-top fade", "Ducktail", "Bangs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what period does your sleep become almost impossible and interrupted.", "correct_answer": "The third trimester", "incorrect_answers": ["The second trimester", "The first month of the pregnancy", "The first trimester"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the only number with no reciprocal?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "-1", "Pi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A US citizen can qualify for both Medicare and Medicaid at the same time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie A Few Good Men, a marine was killed by two fellow marines. What was the  last name of the soldier who was killed?", "correct_answer": "Santiago", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruiz", "Rivera", "Mendoza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saw II, the needle pit test was meant for which character?", "correct_answer": "Xavier", "incorrect_answers": ["Gus", "Amanda", "Obi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Were Jean and Billy in love with each other in the Billy Jack movie?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin A helps to restore the structure of damaged hair.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bernardo Bertoluccis film La Luna focuses on the troubled life of a teenage boy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy hit Anchorman, Ron Burgundy impressed Veronica Corningstone with his vast knowledge of the history of San Diego.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many young pangolins can an adult pangolin have at one time?", "correct_answer": "1-2", "incorrect_answers": ["3-4", "4-5", "2-3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dinosaurs lived during which geologic era?", "correct_answer": "Mesozoic", "incorrect_answers": ["Cretazoic", "Protozoic", "Holozoic"]}]